gifpal.com 2015-12-07

# GIFPAL - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out the data processing practices carried out through the web by the GIFPAL website and Facebook application. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us at info@GIFPAL.com.

## Information collected

Protecting your personal privacy is very important to us, GIFPAL.com collects no personal information about you other than that which you choose to provide when you use the website or the Facebook application, have questions or need help with a particular issue. No individual identifying or personal information (such as your name) is automatically gathered when you visit Any Page of GIFPAL.com

## Webcam and Images Data

Information about your webcams and images captured are not transferred outside your computer unless you choose to save your GIF online or publish in the public gallery. GIFs that you save online but not share in the gallery are never shared with anyone and are removed if not viewed after a certain period.

## Use of personal information by GIFPAL.com

No personal information is collected by the GIFPAL.com website at the moment.

## Disclosures

We will only disclose personal information to other companies within our group of companies and successors in title to our business, unless otherwise agreed.

## Use of personal information by 3rd parties

Your information will never be passed to any 3rd party outside the GIFPAL.com.   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Use of cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. GIFPAL.com website might use cookies.

## Other web sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you that will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

## Facebook

This website and the Facebook application is not developed by Facebook.

## Internet-based transfers

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by using our website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.
